Guide to the Barnett Lipton papers, 1970-1993 MS2062
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Barnett Lipton papers
1970-1993
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Lipton, Barnett
MS2062
11.5 Linear Feet
Collection consists of items relating to events produced by Barnett Lipton as president and creative director of Eventures, as well as those events he produced while he was affiliated with Radio City Music Hall Productions and was involved in as an independent production manager. Some of the most prominent events represented in the collection are the 1984 Los Angeles Olympics and other Olympic Festivals, the 1990 Seattle Goodwill Games, the halftime presentation at Super Bowl XXII, and the 1991 Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade. The materials cover the period from 1970 to 1993, with most of the materials dating from 1988 to 1991.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Lipton donated these items to the Gelman Library of The George Washington University in 1994 and 2000. At the time of the donation, Lipton transferred all rights, such as he held them, to the collection with the exception of copyright.
Historical or Biographical Note
Barnett Lipton is a special events professional who has created productions for the Olympics, other major sporting events, and corporate and private events. Lipton first became involved in the special events industry after graduating from New York University, where he studied scenic design. He began as an independent concert producer and then became a production manager. Hired as the production manager for the Opening and Closing Ceremonies of the 1984 Los Angeles Olympics, his work drew the attention of Radio City Music Hall Productions. Lipton joined the Radio City Music Hall Productions staff and went on to produce numerous special events, one of the most memorable being the halftime show for Super Bowl XXII.
In 1989 Lipton left Radio City Music Hall to form Eventures, Inc., a full-service special events production company in partnership with the Mediators Entertainment Network, a subsidiary of a marketing/media-buying company known as Mediators, Inc. After he was named president and creative director, their first project was the 1989 U.S. Olympic Festival in Norman, Oklahoma. Eventures has gone on to produce many other events, including the 1991 Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade, the 1990 Seattle Goodwill Games, and many other corporate and private events.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection consists of items relating to events produced by Lipton as president and creative director of Eventures, as well as those events he produced while he was affiliated with Radio City Music Hall Productions and was involved in as an independent production manager. Some of the most prominent events represented in the collection are the 1984 Los Angeles Olympics and other Olympic Festivals, the 1990 Seattle Goodwill Games, the halftime presentation at Super Bowl XXII, and the 1991 Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade. The materials cover the period from 1970 to 1993, with most of the materials dating from 1988 to 1991.
Collection items include production manuals, ceremony and parade scripts, elevations, site plans, drawings, photographs, articles, banners, and videotapes of events. In addition, there is a small collection of resource books.
Lipton donated these items to the Gelman Library of The George Washington University in 1994 and 2000. At the time of the donation, Lipton transferred all rights, such as he held them, to the collection with the exception of copyright.
Collection Organization
Organized in two series: the 1994 accession; and the 2000 accretion.
Collection note
Bibliography: 'Event' exec in venture." Advertising Age. 26 June 1989 p. 34. "Ticker-Tape Challenge: Planning the Big Parade." New York Times. 13 May 1991
New York (N.Y.); Los Angeles (Calif.); Photographs; Diaries; Parades & processions; Production management; Events; Super Bowl; Goodwill Games; Olympic Games; Lipton, Barnett; Radio City Music Hall (New York, N.Y.); Eventures, Inc. (Firm)
- 1994 accession, 1970-1993; MS2062 Series 1; 6.5 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains production manuals, ceremony and parade scripts, elevations, site plans, drawings, photographs, banners, and videotapes of events. In addition, there is a small collection of resource books. Materials date from 1970 to 1993, with the majority of items dating from 1988 to 1991.
  - Pageantry Production Manual, Games of the XXIIIrd Olympiad - Los Angeles, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Original Script, First Draft, Opening Ceremonies, XXIIIrd Olympiad, Los Angeles, 07/10/1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Commemorative brochure, Something Grand Halftime Presentation, Super Bowl XXII, 01/31/1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Printed logo for Operation Welcome Home - NYC, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Script, Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of All-City High School Marching Band, New York City, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Francis Lewis High School Band, Queens, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of The Lesbian and Gay Big Apple Corps, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Original Hobo Band, Pitman, NJ, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Palmyra South Jersey String Band, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Cadets of Bergen County Drum and Bugle Corps, Hackensack, NJ, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Ventnor City String Band, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Port Chester High School Marching Band, Port Chester, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Allentown High School Red Bird Marching Band, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Tottenville High School Band, Staten Island, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Westchester Brassmen Drum and Bugle Corps, Harrison, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Nassau County, NY Police Drum and Bugle Corps, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Sword of Light Pipe and Drum Band, New York, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of The Salvation Army Greater New York Division Band, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of County Corkmens Pipe Band, New York City, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Nassau County, NY Police Pipe and Drum Corps, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Staten Island Pipers Pipes and Drums, Staten Island, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Essex Shillelagh Pipes and Drums, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Spirit of Black Rock Fife and Drum Corps, Bridgeport, CT, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Patriots of Northern Virginia Colonial Regiment, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of The New York Ancients Fife and Drum Corps, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Colonial Musketeers Fife and Drum Corps, Hackettstown, NJ, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of 3rd Connecticut Regiment of Fifes and Drums, East Hampton, CT, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Nathan Hale Ancient Fifes and Drums, Coventry, CT, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Brick Township High School Marching Band, Brick, NJ, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Clifton High School Mustang Band, Clifton, NJ, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Ancient Order of Hibernians Pipes and Drums, Rockland County, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Emerald Society of the City of New York Police Pipe Band, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Emerald Society of the City of New York Fire Department Pipes and Drums, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of New York City Transit Police Pipes and Drums, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of New York City Department of Correction Emerald Pipe Band, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of New York City Housing Police Pipes and Drums, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Iona College Pipes and Drums, New Rochelle, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of Medical Center of East Orange, NJ, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of P.S. 172 District 15 Brooklyn, NY, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC Ticker Tape Parade photograph of unidentified band, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Program, Edwin H. Land: A Celebration of His Life, 09/07/1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Show Rundown, Stanford University Centennial Stadium Spectacular, 09/30/1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Program (2 copies), Stanford University Centennial Stadium Spectacular, 09/30/1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Script, Columbus 500 Parade, Philadelphia, PA, 10/11/1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Eventures Brochure,(2 copies), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1993 Brochure, United States Olympic Congress with 2 page letter enclosure, 03/25/1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Medallion inscribed Kimball - Supplier to the 1984 Olympics, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Guess Where the World's Travel Industry will be in 1995..." (2 copies) folder, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cossette wedding guest list, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, XXIII Olympiad - Los Angeles, 2 prints, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, "We the People" float 200th Anniversary of the Declaration of Independence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Super Bowl XXII, 01/31/1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 200th Anniversary of George Washington's Inauguration, 04/30/1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photographs Olympic Festival - Norman, OK, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Photographs Goodwill Games - Seattle, 2 prints, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, One-to-One - NYC, 06/09/1992-06/10/1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Coca-Cola Centennial Celebration, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Unidentified Olympics/Olympic Festival,5 prints, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, New York City fantasy scenes, 2 prints, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Unidentified event, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Banners, Games of the XXIII Olympiad - Los Angeles, 5'x8', 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Banners, "We the People 200", 3'x5', 1787-1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Banners, Seattle Goodwill Games, 3'x4', 1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Banners, Seattle Goodwill Games, 3'x4', 1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Banners, Olympics, interlocking circles, 5'x8', n.d., undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Banners, Gold and white Olympics pennant with star emblem, 3'x4.5', n.d., undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Olympics and Olympic Festivals, Yellow and blue plastic cards for XXIII Olympiad - Los Angeles, Opening Ceremony card stunt 1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Olympics and Olympic Festivals, Red, white, and blue paperboard cards for 1990 U.S. Olympic Festival Opening Ceremony - Twin Cities,07/06/1990, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Plan view and section view of The World Trade Center Communisphere Theatre, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Introduction of Royal Viking Sun at Port of Miami, U-matic, 12/10/1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Royal Viking Sun - San Francisco, VHS, 01/08/1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Jimmy Stewart segment 1989 ET Entertainment Tonight - Royal Viking Sun, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "One to One" New York City, Reel #1,VHS, 06/09/1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "One to One" New York City, Reel #2,VHS, 06/09/1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - "One to One" New York City, Reel #3,VHS, 06/10/1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - "One to One" New York City, Reel #4,VHS, 06/10/1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "One to One" Dinner Video Opener,VHS, 06/02/1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Operation Welcome Home - NYC, The Official Highlight Video, VHS, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Official Highlight Video "Heroes on Parade," VHS, 12/01/1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Operation Welcome Home produced by Barnett Lipton, Channel 2 News, U-matic, 08/10/1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Eventures Demo Reel, U-matic, 06/26/1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - New Year's Eve, Special Effects, U-matic, 04/08/1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - ITT Worldwide Management Conference, U-matic, n.d., undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Kay Crawford Pep Arts Training Series: Dance, VHS, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Kay Crawford Pep Arts Training Series: Field, VHS, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Kay Crawford Pep Arts Training Series: Prop, VHS, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Kay Crawford Pep Arts Training Series: Solo, VHS, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Super Bowl XXII Halftime, VHS, 01/31/1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Super Bowl XXII Halftime Show with The Radio City Rockettes, VHS, 01/31/1988, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Highlights of 200th Anniversary of George Washington's Inauguration, VHS, 04/30/1989, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Stadium Stunts: Singapore Jubilee Celebration, VHS, 08/25/1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Dance in America, The American Indian Dance Theatre, Finding the Circle, VHS, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - A Tribute to Edwin Land, VHS, 09/07/1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Street Scenes: New York on Film, VHS, n.d., undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1989 U.S. Olympic Festival Opening Ceremonies, Norman, OK - Owen Stadium, Reel 1, U-matic, 07/21/1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1989 U.S. Olympic Festival Opening Ceremonies, Norman, OK - Owen Stadium, Reel 2, U-matic, 07/21/1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1989 U.S. Olympic Festival Opening Ceremonies, Norman, OK - Owen Stadium, Reel 3, U-matic, 07/21/1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1989 U.S. Olympic Festival Closing Ceremonies, Norman, OK - Owen Stadium, Reel 1, U-matic, 07/30/1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1989 U.S. Olympic Festival Closing Ceremonies, Norman, OK - Owen Stadium, Reel 2, U-matic, 07/30/1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1989 U.S. Olympic Festival Closing Ceremonies, Norman, OK - Owen Stadium, Reel 3, U-matic, 07/30/1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Highlights U.S. Olympic Festival Ceremonies, U-matic, 07/21/1989-07/30/1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Winning a Place in the World, The Official Commemorative Video of the U.S. Olympic Festival 1989, VHS (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Olympic Festival Opening Ceremonies, 2 hour edited OETA version, VHS, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1980 Olympics Opening Ceremonies,(Moscow) #8, VHS (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1980 Olympics Opening Ceremonies, #9, VHS (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1980 Olympics Opening Ceremonies, #12, VHS (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1980 Olympics Opening Ceremonies, #16, VHS (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1986 Goodwill Games Opening Ceremony, VHS, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1990 Goodwill Games Welcoming Ceremony, Reel 2 of 3, U-matic (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1990 Goodwill Games Welcoming Ceremony, Reel 3 of 3, U-matic (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1990 Goodwill Games Closing Ceremony, Part I, U-matic (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Movie Clips, n.d., undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Book, America's Biggest Birthday Party: V.P. Fair St. Louis. St. Louis: Indian Paintbrush, Inc., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Book, DiGrazia, Carlo Alberto. Viareggio: Follie di Carnevale. Viareggio: L'Ancora, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Book, Gall, Herbert. Perfecting the Marching Band: Techniques and Procedures for Marching Musical Units of All Sizes. New York: Abelard-Schuman, Photocopy in looseleaf binder, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Book, Kahan, Nancy. Entertaining for Business. New York: Clarkson N. Potter, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Book, Morescalchi, Alfredo. Ricordi di un Carnevalaro. Viareggio: La Nuov Europa, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Book, National Anthems of the United Nations and their Allies. Boston: Boston Music Co., 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Book, Plimpton, George. Fireworks: A History and Celebration. Garden City: Doubleday & Co., Inc., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Book, Tobino, Mario, Pellegrini, Renzo, and DiGrazia, Carlo Alberto. Il Carnelvale di Viareggio. Milan: Arnoldo Mondadori, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Book, Ukman, Lisa, ed. 1994 IEG Directory of Sponsorship Marketing. 6th ed. Chicago: International Events Group, Inc. Spiral bound, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Book, V.P. Fair in Review A Photographic History Commemorating the 10th Anniversary of the V.P. Fair. St. Louis: Indian Paintbrush, Inc., 1981-1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Book, Wilkinson, David G. The Event Management and Marketing Institute. Toronto: The Event Management and Marketing Institute, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Renaissance Night Plan, 12/06/1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Sheet 2, General Sessions Plan, 12/06/1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Sheet 3, California Night Plan, 12/07/1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Sheet 4, Super Bowl Plan, 12/06/1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Sheet 6, Banquet Plan, 12/06/1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Sheet 7, Sections: Business Mtg.; Banquet; Super Bowl; Special C.M.M., 12/03/1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Sheet 8, Show Deck, 12/03/1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Sheet 9, D.S. Light Boxes & Skin Flats; Screen Surround; Speaker Maskings, 12/03/1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Sheet 10, Upstage Travelling Flats; Midstage Travelling Flats; Football Helmet; Pipe/Drapery - Super Bowl Screen Unit, 12/14/1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, .Sheet 11, Hard Borders; Soft Border Covers; Truss Mask Flats; Banquet Cyl. & Scrim, 12/03/1990 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, .Sheet 12, Production Booths; Lecterns, 12/03/1990 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Sheet 13, M. Hamlisch Orch. Risers; L. Brown Orch. Risers; L. Brown Mask Flats; L. Brown Drapery, 12/04/1990 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - ITT Special C.M.M. Elevations, Sheet 1, Sheet 14, Special C.M.M. Desk; Drive-in Movie Screen & Surround Flats; Chubby Checker Stage, 12/17/1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Operation Welcome Home Parade Plan View, City Hall Park, (NYC Parade) n.d., undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Operation Welcome Home Parade Plan View, City Hall Park, (NYC Parade) n.d., undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Operation Welcome Home Parade Possible Signage Locations, Jeep Sahara,(2 copies) (NYC Parade), 05/12/1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Operation Welcome Home Parade Reviewing Stand Facings Elevation,(NYC Parade), 05/11/1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Operation Welcome Home Parade Reviewing Stand Elevation, Color, (NYC Parade) n.d., undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Operation Welcome Home Parade Plan View, Reviewing Stand Facings (photocopy)(NYC Parade), n.d., undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Operation Welcome Home Parade Elevation, Press Platforms, (NYC Parade) n.d., undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Operation Welcome Home Parade Elevation, Reviewing Stand Facings and Elevation, Press Platforms,(NYC Parade), 05/11/1991 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Operation Welcome Home Parade photograph, (NYC Parade), 06/10/1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Centennial Spectacular - Stanford Stadium Site Plan, 09/01/1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Centennial Spectacular, photograph, 09/30/1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Centennial Spectacular, photograph, 09/30/1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Columbus 500th Anniversary Parade, 5 chalk drawings, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Columbus 500th Anniversary Parade, 1 chalk drawing, n.d., undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Columbus 500th Anniversary Parade - Philadelphia, PA, photograph of drawing with logo, n.d., undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Trump Taj Majal Caravan photograph of drawing, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 1992 Democratic Convention - Media Welcoming Event Plan, 06/16/1992 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Six panel matted drawings, "Stars & Stripes Forever," and "Always Home," n.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Olympics event chalk drawing, n.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
- 2000 accretion, 1987-1993; MS2062 Series 2; 5 Linear feet
  This series contains newspaper and magazine articles, photographs, brochures, programs, award certificates, videotapes, sketches, and oversized graphics. It dates from 1987 to 1993, with the majority of items dating from 1989 to 1991.
  - 200th Anniversary of George Washington's Inauguration-Final report, NYC, 04/30/1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 200th Anniversary of George Washington's Inauguration-articles, NYC, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Program-Opening Ceremonies-US Olympic Festival, Norman OK, 07/21/1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Opening Ceremonies-US Olympic Festival, articles, Norman OK, 07/1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Opening Ceremonies-US Olympic Festival, photograph, Norman OK, 07/21/1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Closing Ceremony-US Olympic Festival, Norman OK, articles, 07/1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Closing Ceremony-US Olympic Festival, photograph, Norman OK, 07/30/1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Winning Times-US Olympic Festival, Norman OK, 07/1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - US Olympic Festival, Norman OK, general articles, 07/1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Breaking records-US Olympic Festival, Norman OK, articles, 07/1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cartoons-US Olympic Festival, Norman OK, 07/1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Complimentary Correspondence-US Olympic Festival, Norman OK, 07/1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Most Outstanding Spectacle Award, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Nomination for Best Event Coordinated for a Nonprofit Organization, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Recognition Award, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Official Logo-US Olympic Festival, Twin Cities MN, 07/1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Opening Ceremonies Program-US Olympic Festival, Twin Cities MN, 07/06/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Opening Ceremonies-US Olympic Festival, articles, Twin Cities MN, 07/1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Opening Ceremonies-US Olympic Festival, photograph, Twin Cities MN, 07/06/1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - US Olympic Festival, general articles, Twin Cities MN, 07/1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)